(Amy:)I think it'll be fine.
(Sheldon:)Very well, then.
(Sheldon:)I'll see you
on Thanksgiving morning.
(Amy:)See you then.
Oh,
(Sheldon:)and forget what I said
about the Myanmar catfish.
(Sheldon:)My list of marine-themed
pilgrim facts is pretty short.
(Amy:)Did you know they served
shellfish and eel
(Amy:)at the very first Thanksgiving?
(Sheldon:)And there goes my list.
(Emily:)So, how does this work?
(Bernadette:)The soup kitchen manager
assigns the jobs,
(Bernadette:)and the shifts
are six hours.
(Howard:)Six hours?
(Howard:)Oh, God, I don't want to
complain for that long.
(Raj:)Do you ever do anything
for anyone else?
(Howard:)I happen to be
a giving and generous lover.
(Emily:)Are you and I close enough
for me to say that's creepy?
(Bernadette:)We are, and I believe the word
you're looking for is... yech!
(Soup Kitchen Manager:)Uh, can I help you?
(Bernadette:)Hi. We'd like to volunteer.
(Soup Kitchen Manager:)Oh, I appreciate
you guys coming down,
(Soup Kitchen Manager:)but we already have
enough people.
(Soup Kitchen Manager:)Any other day,
please, come back.